饑餓
的青春
第二季  第十八集
0,0,0,fx,學習
0,0,0,fx,分享
0,0,0,fx,進步
翻譯   roaddog  aaaBao
翻譯  冰藍
校對  roaddog
時間軸 aaaBao
后期 斯人       總監 roaddog
打開微信   掃描左側二維碼
早上好
Good morning.
早上...
Good mor--
很好吃  對吧
Yeah, it's good, right?
這是手做杏仁奶油
It's artisanal almond butter.
首先  我覺得這很厲害
Well, "A", I'm really impressed
你居然知道怎么用"手做"這個詞
that you know how to use the word "artisanal."
其次  杏仁奶油
And "B", umm, almond butter?
一罐要十五塊呢  我們吃不起
It's $15 a jar! We can't afford it!
靠這個就行了
Not with this.
所以你買了臺六百塊的料理機
Oh, okay, so you bought a $600 Vitamix
來做十五塊的杏仁奶油嗎
to make $15 worth of almond butter?
是啊
Yup.
我打算開始新業務
I'm starting this new thing
制作不同種類的果仁奶油
where I make different types of nut butters,
然后在灣區的農貿市場出售
and I sell them at farmers markets all over the bay area.
是嗎
Are ya?
是的
Yes, I are.
你真是瘋了[堅果]
Aww, you're nuts.
我可以拿這句話做廣告呢
Hey, that could be my catchphrase.
加比  你知道買堅果  罐子
Gabi, do you have any idea how much it would cost to buy the nuts,
絲帶  標簽  保險  還有銷售許可證
the jars, the ribbons, the tag, the insurance,
需要多少錢嗎
let alone the permits for selling?
我有個主意
Oh, I have an idea!
我們來發明計算機吧
Let's invent the computer.
不不不  必須碾壓創新
Oh, no, no, no! It's important that innovation be crushed!
加比  我不想碾壓你的夢想
Gabi, I'm not trying to crush your dreams.
只是我們沒有錢
It's just that money is, you know-- we don't have any.
所以這個主意完全不現實
So, this idea is just totally unrealistic.
"這個主意完全不現實"
"This idea is totally unrealistic."
我跟你說吧
I'll tell you what.
-我對你買料理機沒意見  -好
- I'll be fine with you buying this-- - Yes.
前提是你以"一分都沒"回答下一個問題
...if you answer "none" to the following question.
我們還有十一天就要交房租了
How much of our rent, which is due in 11 days,
你花了多少租金買這六百塊的料理機
have you spent on this $600 blender?
夢想終結者
Dream crusher.
早上好  姑娘
Morning, girl.
怎么了
What's the matter?
索菲亞想讓我退了這臺料理機
Sofia wants me to return this Vitamix,
但人家真的好想要
but I really want it.
我還想跟丹澤爾和勒布朗3P呢
Yeah, well, I wand to he the meat in a Denzel-LeBron sandwich,
但我們不會一直如愿
but we don't always get what we want.
有時候會因為嘗試而被逮捕
And sometimes, we get arrested trying.
瞧瞧我為同志驕傲周末買的衣服
Check out the outfit I got for gay pride weekend.
你想把他們嚇直嗎
You trying to scare them straight?
瞧瞧我要穿的
Look what I'm wearing.
那輛游行花車為什么帶著你的假發啊
Why is that parade float wearing your wig?
那是我啦
That's me!
你為什么去同志驕傲節啊
Why are you going to pride?
還記得你騙我扮成了
Oh, remember when you tricked me into
變裝賓果游戲主持人嗎
being a drag queen bingo host?
真好玩
Ha, that was funny.
現在我成了同志偶像
Well, now, I am a gay icon.
全城都有男人請我喝酒
I got men buying me drinks all over town.
因為他們覺得你是男人
Because they think you're a man.
如果12碼的鞋能穿上的話
Well, if the size 12 shoe fits.
我有個想法
Hey, here's a thought.
埃蘭出城了  不如我們一起去吧
Since Allan's out of town, why don't we go together?
我想慶祝的是驕傲  不是羞恥
I want to celebrate pride. Not shame.
不  尤蘭達  想想吧
No. Yolanda, think about it.
我是個超棒的公關
I'm an amazing publicist.
我可以搞到節前派對
I can get us invites to the pre-party,
游行派對和節后派對的邀請
the parade party, and the post-party.
你可以為我們搞到免費的酒
You can get us free drinks.
我們會是驕傲游行上最受歡迎的一對
We'll be the most popular pair of people at the pride parade.
我喜歡
Ooh, I like it.
我的公寓位于活動中心
And my apartment sits in the center of all the action,
我們可以每場派對都穿不同的衣服了
so we can change outfits for every event!
真棒  這內褲我有好多不同的圖案
Perfect! I own this in many patterns.
幸虧我沒有把房子租出去
Oh, you know, thank god I didn't rent my place out.
有人說想在周末租我的房子  開價六百塊
You know, someone offered me $600 for the weekend?
有人開價六百塊租你的房子嗎
Somebody offered you $600 to rent out your place?
是啊  我的公寓能看見游行全景
That's right. My apartment has a view of the whole parade.
人們愿意為此付錢
And people are willing to pay cash dollar money for that.
那就是說我的公寓也能看到值錢景色啦
So, that means my apartment has a cash dollar money view.
你聽到了嗎
Are you hearing this?
天啊
Oh... my god!
各位
Guys...
我剛收到了ED演講的邀請
I just got invited to an EDtalk.
恭喜  這可是大事啊
Congratulations! This is huge!
太棒了
Wow, that's amazing!
如果知道那是什么  我會更加真誠的
If I knew what it was, I'd be more sincere.
加比  ED演講
Gabi, an EDtalk
就是他們邀請非常成功的人士
is when they invite this extremely successful person
發表鼓舞人心的演講  他們進行直播
to give this inspirational speech, and they livestream it.
如果火了  這可能改變一切
If it goes viral, this could be a game changer.
真有趣
Fun!
每段優秀的ED演講都有令人震撼的一刻
Every great EDtalk has this moment that is so mind-blowing,
全體觀眾都會倒抽一口氣
the entire audience gasps.
不止如此  我還有絕妙的開場笑話
I don't only have that, but I have a killer opening joke.
聽好了
Check it.
為什么計算機下班回家以后精疲力盡
Why was the computer stressed out when it got home from work?
因為它開了很久車[有硬盤]
'Cause it had a hard drive.
羅杰  你先說  然后喬什跟上
Roger, you'll be speaking first, and then Josh will follow.
你們想要講臺升起還是降下去
Do you guys want the podium up or down?
我要升起
I'll go up.
我不要
Not me.
史蒂夫·喬布斯的講臺是降下去的
See, Steve Jobs had it down.
達賴喇嘛也是
Dalai Lama had it down.
喬什·卡明斯基也要降下去
And Josh Kaminski? He's gonna have it down.
我不想讓我和觀眾之間有阻礙
I want nothing between me and my audience.
天啊
Oh, brother.
知道嗎  各位
You know what, guys?
我為你們準備了小禮物
I got a little treat for you.
湊近點  我分享一下我的開場笑話
I want you to come close. I'm going to share my opening joke.
為什么計算機下班回家以后精疲力盡
Why was the computer stressed out when it got home?
因為它開了很久車[有硬盤]
'Cause it had a hard drive. Bam!
這玩意兒顯然壞了
Well, this thing's obviously broken.
加比  已經三天了  料理機怎么還在
Gabi, it's been three days. Why is the blender still here?
記得你說過
Well, remember when you said
如果我能想辦法不用房租
that if I could figure out a way to pay for the blender
付料理機的錢  就能留下它嗎
without using our rent money, I could keep it?
-記得  -我做到了
- Yeah. - Well, I did it!
你做了什么
You did what?
喬什周末不在家  去做演講了
Well, Josh is away for the weekend doing some sort of talk.
他讓我幫他看家
And he asked me to house sit.
-好的  -與此同時
- Okay. - Meanwhile,
我們自己家這里
over here at our place,
將舉行驕傲游行
it's gay pride,
要是你家能看到游行現場
and if you have a view of the parade,
就能以六百元的價格租出去
you can rent out your place for $600.
猜猜我們能看到什么
And guess what we have?
游行現場
A view of the parade!
問題解決  能留下這臺豪華料理機了
Problem solved, the fancy blender stays.
加比贏了
Gabi for the win.
加比  首先我得說
Gabi, first, let me say
我欣賞你的確想出了一個好辦法
that I appreciate that you actually came up with a sensible plan.
我知道  我知道
I know. I know.
但是有一個問題
But there's just one problem.
我不想讓陌生人住在我家
I don't want strangers staying in my place,
碰我的東西
touching my things,
睡在我床上  留下口水和...子孫
sleeping in my bed with their drool and their parts.
但是索菲亞...
But Sofia--
不行  加比  沒人可以住在這
No, Gabbi, the answer is no. Nobody can stay here.
我們可能遇到了點麻煩
We may have a little bit of a situation.
你把我們的房子租出去了嗎
You rent our apartment?
租給了特別好的人
To really cool people.
可能是吧
Probably.
你們好  聽著  我很抱歉...
Hi. Listen, I'm really sorry--
-你好  -你好
- Hi. - Hi.
-她們就這么進來了  -你好
- And they're in. - Hi.
-我叫薩姆  -我叫格蕾茜
- I'm Sam. - And I'm Gracie.
你們家真漂亮
This place is so cute.
跟照片上的一樣
Just like all the pictures.
這算不上是個陽臺
Well, this is hardly a veranda.
幸運地是  你們家能看到這次游行
Luckily, you guys have a view of the parade.
她弟弟是這次游行的大禮官
Her brother's the grand marshal.
天吶  索菲亞也有一個基佬弟弟
Oh, my God! Sofia has a gay brother, too!
基佬兄弟們萬歲
Yay for gay brothers!
我也不想破壞大家的興致
Okay, well, I hate to break it to everybody,
但是作為這間房子的共同居住者
but as co-habitant of said apartment,
我的室友沒有告訴我
I was not informed by the other co-habitant of this apartment
把房子轉租給別人這件事
about this sub-leasing situation,
所以我得請你們離開
so I'm gonna have to ask you to leave.
不是吧  你的室友有沒有告訴你我們簽了合同
Really? Well, did your co-habitant tell you we have a contract?
你簽了合同嗎
You signed a contract?
對  可是你挺喜歡合同的啊
Yeah, but you love contracts!
我...氣死我了  都不知道該從哪說起了
I-- I'm so mad right now, I don't even know where to start.
索菲亞  冷靜一下好嗎  我有別的辦法
Sofia, hang on, okay? I have another idea.
既然你不愿意讓她們住在這  她們也不想走
Since you don't want them here, and they don't want to leave,
不如給她們升個房
how about we upgrade them
住到我老板的高層豪華公寓怎么樣
to my boss' deluxe apartment in the sky?
這主意不錯
That sounds so amazing!
不不不  我不想住高層
No, no, no, I don't want to be in the sky.
我想在這里看游行
I want to be here with the view of the parade.
不是吧  現在你把喬什的房子給她們住嗎
Seriously, so now you're just offering Josh's apartment?
真不敢相信  加比
I-- I can't believe you, Gabi.
你猜怎么著  我...
You know what? I--
事實上  你的確做得出這種事
Actually, I can believe it!
因為你一直做這樣的事情
Because you do things like this all the time!
如果你不總是拒絕我的話
Well, I wouldn't do things like this all the time
我也不會一直做這種事
if you didn't always say no.
要是你不像個不負責任的孩子
I wouldn't have to say no, Gabi,
加比  我也不會拒絕你
if you weren't acting like an irresponsible child.
天吶  你什么時候變得那么嚴厲
Oh, my God. When did you get such a stick up your ass?
不知道  或許是你逼我的
I don't know, maybe you put it there without asking me.
這是怎么了  索菲亞
What's happening, Sofia?
我們以前很開心  一起出去玩  一起做傻事
We used to have fun and hang out and do stupid stuff together.
我們成熟了  加比
We grew up, Gabi,
至少我成熟了
Or at least I did.
要是成熟意味著像你一樣  那我寧愿不成熟
Well, if growing up means acting like you, then I don't want to.
這正是問題的關鍵
And that's exactly the point.
我成熟了  而你沒有
I've grown up, and you haven't.
或許事實上我們越來越疏遠了
So, maybe the truth is we've just actually grown apart.
也許是這樣
Oh, well, maybe we have.
抱歉讓你們目睹這一切
I'm sorry you had to see that.
沒關系
Oh, it's okay.
我們剛在車里也為這吵了一架
We just had the same argument in the car.
我和她越來越疏遠了
I'm growing apart from her?
我是滿腦子蠢主意的孩子嗎
I'm a child with stupid ideas?
看看這蠢不蠢
Well, how stupid is this?
蠢得太贊了
Stupid awesome!
天吶
Oh, my God.
真高興我決定跟你一起來這
I am so glad I decided to come with you.
是啊
Yeah, you are.
謝謝你讓我住在...我的家里
Thank you so much for letting me stay in... my apartment.
希望我嚴厲的性格不會嚇到你
I hope the stick up my ass doesn't get in your way.
別這么說
Oh, please.
以格蕾茜指出的我的嚴厲之處[屁股上的棍子]
With all the sticks Gracie's told me I have up my ass,
都夠我開個冰棍廠了
I could start a popsicle factory.
天吶  你旅行還自帶杯墊嗎
Oh, my God. You travel with your own coasters?
是的  是不是很瘋狂
Yeah, is that crazy?
瘋得太棒了
It's crazy awesome!
我從來沒到過這么高的地方[這么嗨過]
I've never been this high before.
開玩笑的  我絕對有過
Just kidding. I totally have.
真好笑
That's really funny.
索菲亞也說過這樣的笑話
You know, Sofia used to make jokes like that.
現在她唯一說的笑話就是
Now, the only joke she makes is,
"砰砰  誰在敲門
"Knock, knock. Who's there?
閉嘴  我們分手[碎]了"
Shut up, we're broke."
上周  加比...
And last week, Gabi--
加比給我發短信了
Oh, it's Gabi texting me.
或許是想道歉
Probably wanting to apologize.
不  是一張她屁股的照片
Nope, it's just a picture of her butt.
你想讓她回來嗎
You want to get her back?
別理她  做個成熟的人
Ignore her. Be the bigger person.
我怎么沒早點遇到你
Where have you been all my life?
她們回你的短信了嗎
What did they text back?
沒  她們想不出如何反駁
Nothing. They can't think of a comeback.
-她們真沒勁  -是啊
- They're so boring. - I know.
你知道什么有意思嗎
Hey, you know what's not boring?
優惠券
Couponing!
-瑪格麗塔酒  -沒錯
- Margaritas! - Yeah!
能休息一下真好
Oh, it's good to take a little break.
-你要休息了嗎  -不  你呢
- Oh, you need a break? - No, do you?
-不用  -明白了
- No. - Gotcha.
我能每天都像這樣參加派對
I could party like this every day.
我也是
Me too.
我的心臟要爆炸了
My heart feels like it's about to explode.
高興激動的爆炸了
From all the fun and excitement.
我的腳也在抽筋
And my feet are throbbing.
跟著電子樂的節奏舞動
To the rhythm of the techno.
你猜怎么著  我們去換衣服吧
You know what? Let's go change outfits,
然后繼續下去游行
So we can get back out there.
沒錯
You know it.
不過你還知道嗎
But, you know what else?
我發現站在這能看到更多游行隊伍
I'm noticing you get a better view of the parade from right here.
真好奇坐下來看會不會更好
I wonder if it's even better sitting down?
我看看
Let me see.
但就坐一小會
But just for a brief mo.
隨著我們的生活日趨便捷
So, as our lives become easier,
為我們服務的計算機
The computers doing our jobs
才是需要診療的對象
will be the ones who'll need therapy.
有了我的算法  它們將會痊愈
And thanks to my algorithm, they'll be able to get it.
這讓我想起一個笑話
Reminds me of a joke.
為什么計算機下班回家以后精疲力盡
Why was the computer stressed out when it got home from work?
因為它開了很久車[有硬盤]
'cause it had a hard drive.
你聽到了嗎
Did you hear that?
不  他剽竊了我的笑話
No. No, he stole my joke!
天啊  你說得好對
My gosh, you're so right.
喊幾個朋友來玩真的能放松
Having a few friends over totally mellowed me out.
或者是因為這一大壺瑪格麗塔酒
Or maybe it's the pitcher of margaritas?
這也有用
That too.
馬上更多的朋友就要來了  真好玩
Oh, some more margarita drinkers are on their way up. Fun!
是我老板電話
Oh, it's my boss.
你帶他們進來  我來對付他
You buzz your friends in, I'll handle this guy.
老板
Hey, boss.
加比  這就是災難
Gabi, this is a disaster!
我想給艾略特打電話  但他不接
I'm trying to call Elliot, and he's not picking up.
怎么了
What's wrong?
在我前面發言的人剽竊了我笑話
The guy before me stole my joke!
什么  他為什么要剽竊那...
What? Why would he steal that...
那么棒的笑話
awesome joke.
就是因為它棒啊  加比
Because of its awesomeness, Gabi.
現在該我上臺了
And now, I'm about to go on,
卻發生了很奇怪的事
and something weird is happening to me.
我手在抖  開始出汗
My hands are shaking, I'm starting to sweat.
那只是怯場而已  好嗎
Okay, well, it's just stage fright, okay?
誰都會這樣的
It happens to everybody.
我不會
Not me.
我胸口好悶
Oh, wow, my chest is tight.
好  你深呼吸
Okay, just take a deep breath.
如果你演講時候還緊張
If it gets bad during your talk,
就想象觀眾穿著內衣的樣子
just picture the audience in their underwear.
開心果  該你上場了
Hey, funny man, you're on.
我要上場了
Oh, I gotta go on.
我就說該把口琴帶來
I knew I should have brought my harmonica.
天啊  天啊
Oh, my god. Oh, my god!
格蕾茜
Gracie?
格蕾茜  你說會來幾個朋友的
Gracie! Gracie, you said a few of your friends were coming up.
別急  剩下的馬上就到
Oh, calm down. The rest will be here real soon.
下面請歡迎  喬什·卡明斯基
Please welcome to the ED stage, Josh Kaminski.
伙計  該你上了
Dude, you're on.
我說把講臺降下去的  算了
I said podium down! Oh, never mind.
大家好
Hi.
我是喬什·卡明斯基
I'm Josh Kaminski.
然后...
And, uh...
今天...我想跟大家聊聊...
today, I'd like to... talk to you about...
聊聊...
about...
真的管用
It worked.
今天我想跟大家聊聊
Today, I would like to talk to you
通向成功的不同途徑
about alternate paths to success.
下去啊  小子
Down, boy.
我們如何衡量成功
How do we measure succ-sex?
嘿咻  嘿咻
Sex. Sex.
成功
Success.
很困難
Well, it's hard.
真的很困難  希望它沒這么難[硬]
It is really hard. I wish it wasn't hard...
但就是難
But it is.
每個人都有自己的成功之路
We each have our own path.
路上是一馬平川嗎  未必
Is it straight? Not always.
這條路漫長嗎  付出就有收獲
Is it long? Everything's relative!
我要的可不是這種抽氣聲
Not the gasp I was hoping for.
真是險
What a rush.
不敢相信我以前從沒用過優惠券
I can't believe I've never couponed before.
現在知道了吧
You would never know it.
謝謝你
Thank you.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
倒走屬于我的清潔劑
Oh, just taking my share of the pine sol.
-你的嗎  -對
- Your share? - Yeah.
是你買的  但我用優惠券幫你省了四毛錢
You bought it, but I saved you 40 cents with my coupon,
所以我要倒走四毛錢的
so just taking my 40 cents worth.
很公平
It's fair.
或許是公平
Well, it might be fair,
但你不覺得有點瘋狂嗎
but it's a little insane, don't you think?
我明白了
Oh, I get it.
是因為我沒付你油錢
This is because I didn't pay you for gas.
不  才五個街區  我不會收你油錢的
Oh, no, no. I drove five blocks. I wouldn't charge you for gas.
可能你收了
Well, maybe if you did,
就不至于會在網上把房子
you wouldn't have to rent your house out to strangers
租給陌生人了
on the internet.
這是怎么回事
What's happening here?
我以為我們挺默契
I thought we were on the same page.
我頭開始疼了
And I think I'm getting a headache.
你要阿司匹林嗎
Oh, you want some aspirin?
好的  謝謝
Uh, yeah, thanks.
-給  -謝謝
- Here you go. - Thank you.
五毛七分錢
That'll be 57 cents.
你們知道真正有意思的是什么嗎
Hey, you know what would be really fun?
所有人都滾蛋
If everybody left!
格蕾茜
Gracie!
加比
Gabi!
等等  你怎么還穿著胸罩
Wait, why are you still wearing a bra?
這里到底怎么回事
What the hell is happening?
你得讓所有人都出去
You gotta get everybody out of here!
幾個人而已啦
Oh, it's just a couple of people.
我朋友賈里德覺得你很可愛
And my friend Jared thinks you're really cute.
真的嗎
Really?
不行
No!
你得讓大家都離開
You gotta get everybody out.
等等  你怎么了
Wait, what's happening to you?
變得跟索菲亞一樣
You're turning into such a Sofia.
索菲亞
Sofia?
我像索菲亞嗎
I'm a Sofia?
如果我變得像索菲亞
If I'm turning into a Sofia,
那唯一的原因就是你像...
the only reason is because you're acting like a--
天啊
Oh, my god.
你剛才是連說了十二遍索菲亞嗎
Did you just say "Sofia," like, 12 times?
還是我真的太醉了
Or am I really wasted?
天啊  是我老板
Oh, my god. Oh, my god, it's my boss!
救命
Help!
喬什  好安靜對不對  你怎么了
Hey, Josh. Pretty quiet. What's going on there?
總而言之就是演講沒有預期的效果
Let's just say the ED talk didn't go as planned.
我要回家了
I'm coming home.
什么  回家嗎
What? Home?
喬什  肯定沒事的  是你對自己太嚴厲
Josh, I'm sure it was fine. You're always so hard on yourself.
你根本想不到
You have no idea.
我馬上就走
I'm leaving right now.
但今天不是周日啊  你說周日回來
But-- but it's not Sunday, and you said Sunday.
加比  我只想蜷在床上
Gabi, all I wanna do is crawl into my bed
再也不見任何人
and never see anyone ever again.
半小時后見
See you in 30 minutes.
天啊
Oh, god...
請幫幫我
Please help.
告訴我個把那些人趕走的辦法
Show me a way to get those people out of there
我發誓我每周都會去教堂
and I promise I'll go to church every week.
每隔一周吧
Every other week.
索菲亞  你怎么來了
Sofia, what are you doing here?
那個薩姆太神經了
That Sam was wound way too tight.
對  格蕾茜也瘋了
Yeah, and Gracie is out of control.
她辦了個派對  喬什已經在回來的路上
She threw a party, and now Josh is on his way here,
屋子里有好多人
and there's like a gazillion people in there,
他們都不肯走
and they won't leave!
這都怪我  我要丟工作了  你得幫我
This is all my fault. I'm gonna lose my job. You gotta help me.
或許我是很嚴厲[屁股上有棍子]
Well, I might have a stick up my ass,
但他們屁股上也要有腳印了
But they're about to have a foot up theirs.
索菲亞  你該怎么辦
Sofia, I don't know what you're gonna do.
這些人都徹底玩瘋了
I mean, these people are totally out of control!
我們不可能趕得走他們
We're never gonna get them out of here.
各位
People!
在下索菲亞·瑪利亞·康斯薇拉
I am Sofia Maria Consuela
拉斐爾·羅德里格斯
Rafaella Rodriguez,
你們該走了
And you're done!
怎么回事
What's going on?
不要  喬什  人家訂婚了
No, Josh, I'm engaged.
怎么了
What's happening?
天啊  我們錯過了
Oh, god. We missed it.
游行真的是與我們擦肩而過
The parade has literally passed us by.
艾略特  我要說實話
Elliot, I have a confession to make.
這個周末太累人了
This holiday is exhausting.
上帝造人  就不是讓他們跳舞十分鐘以上的
Man wasn't made to dance for more than 10 minutes.
這種慶典該有能坐的地方
Celebrations should have places to sit.
面對現實吧
Let's face it,
我們老了
we're old.
沒錯
Yes.
但是  本著驕傲的精神
But, in the spirit of pride,
我們要展現真實的自己
let's be honest about who we are.
我們老了  累了  你們接受吧
We're old! We're tired! Get used to it!
老了才不好  干什么都很難
It doesn't get any better! It gets harder!
我染頭發
I dye my hair!
我戴假發
I buy mine!
-喬什  -怎么了
- Hi, Josh. - Hey, what's up?
沒有  沒什么
Nothing! Nothing's up.
真是噩夢
What a nightmare.
還用說
Tell me about it.
這周末本該很棒的
This weekend was supposed to be so great.
結果成了災難
It turned into a disaster.
-沒錯  -絕對的
- I hear you. - Totally get it.
我從沒覺得自己這么赤裸又脆弱過
I have never felt so naked and exposed.
還有傷心
And sad.
孤獨
And alone.
就像是你以為知道自己在做什么
It's like you think you know what you're doing.
計劃好了一切
You got it all planned out.
對  你知道計劃不是壞事
Yeah, but you know there's nothing wrong with planning.
有計劃是好的
Planning can be good.
然后憑空出現了個東西
And then something pops up out of nowhere
讓你猝不及防
and takes you completely by surprise.
但驚喜也沒什么不對
But there's nothing wrong with surprises.
驚喜可以很有趣
You know, surprises can be fun.
但你知道什么很棒嗎
But, hey, you know what's great?
能回到家
Being able to come home
跟讓你覺得舒心的人在一起
and be with people who make you feel good.
我好想你
Oh, I missed you so much!
我更想你
I missed you more!
我才離開三小時啊
I've only been gone like three hours.
我好愛你
I love you so much!
我更愛你
I love you more!
這樣真好
This is nice.
很鼓舞人心
This is uplifting.
可能有點太鼓舞了
Maybe a little too uplifting.
別又來啊  別又來
Not again, not again, not again...
艾略特  我的演講徹底失敗了
Elliot, my speech was a complete failure.
演講是失敗
Your speech was,
但你的神曲可成功了
But your song's a raging success.
你在說什么
What are you talking about?
作為你的公關  我自己動手
As your publicist, I took matters into my own hands
扭轉了局面
to get in front of the story.
大家好  我是喬什·卡明斯基
Hi, I'm Josh Kaminski.
我們如何衡量成功
How do we measure success?
它很困難  困難  困難
Well, it's hard, hard, hard.
真的很困難  希望它沒這么難
Really hard. I wish it wasn't hard,
但就是難
but it is.
生活中  你要自己動手  動手
In life, you have to be hands on, hands on,
你要自己動手  動手
you have to be hands on, hands on.
這真棒  你一定忙了很久吧
I mean, that's really good. That must've taken you forever.
沒錯  可困難了
Yeah. It was really hard.